<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScaleType Demo</string>

    <string name="image_size">Image Size</string>
    <string name="small">Small</string>
    <string name="wide">Wide</string>
    <string name="tall">Tall</string>
    <string name="user">User</string>

    <string name="scale_type">ScaleType</string>
    <string name="fit_center">FIT_CENTER</string>
    <string name="fit_start">FIT_START</string>
    <string name="fit_end">FIT_END</string>
    <string name="fit_xy">FIT_XY</string>
    <string name="center">CENTER</string>
    <string name="center_crop">CENTER_CROP</string>
    <string name="center_inside">CENTER_INSIDE</string>
    <string name="matrix">MATRIX</string>

    <string
        name="fit_center_desc"><i><b>FIT_CENTER</b> computes a scale that maintains the original
         source aspect ratio, but also ensures that source fits entirely inside destination. At
        least one axis (X or Y) will fit exactly. The result is centered inside destination.</i>
        \n\nNote that all of the images are displayed in the middle with letter-boxing on either
        the top/bottom or sides.
    </string>

    <string
        name="fit_start_desc"><i><b>FIT_START</b> computes a scale that maintains the original
        source aspect ratio, but also ensures that source fits entirely inside destination. At
        least one axis (X or Y) will fit exactly. START aligns the result to the left and top
        edges of destination.</i>
        \n\nNote that all of the images are displayed on the top or left with letter-boxing on
        the opposing side.
    </string>

    <string
        name="fit_end_desc"><i><b>FIT_END</b> computes a scale that maintains the original source
        aspect ratio, but also ensures that source fits entirely inside destination. At least one
        axis (X or Y) will fit exactly. END aligns the result to the right and bottom edges of
        destination.</i>
        \n\nNote that all of the images are displayed on the bottom or right with letter-boxing
        on the opposing side.
    </string>

    <string
        name="fit_xy_desc"><i><b>FIT_XY</b> scales X and Y independently, so that source matches
        destination exactly. This may change the aspect ratio of the source.</i>
        \n\nNote that all of the images are shrunk/stretched to fill the area exactly.
    </string>

    <string
        name="center_desc"><i><b>CENTER</b> centers the image in the view, but  performs no
        scaling.</i>
        \n\nNote that neither dimension of any of the images is scaled and that this results in
        extra white-space all around the small image, but cropping of the longer dimension for
        each the wide and tall images. Note also that the sides are cropped for the still-too wide
        tall image, but that the top and bottom contain extra white-space for the wide image.
    </string>

    <string
        name="center_crop_desc"><i>The <b>CENTER_CROP</b> ScaleType scales the image uniformly
        (maintaining the image\'s aspect ratio) so that both dimensions (width and height) of the
        image will be equal to or larger than the corresponding dimension of the view (minus
        padding). The image is then centered in the view.</i>
        \n\nNote that shorter dimension of each of the images fits the view dimension exactly,
        while the longer dimension of each is cropped-off.
    </string>

    <string
        name="center_inside_desc"><i>The <b>CENTER_INSIDE</b> ScaleType scales the image uniformly
        (maintaining the image\'s aspect ratio) so that both dimensions (width and height) of the
        image will be equal to or less than the corresponding dimension of the view (minus
        padding). The image is then centered in the view.</i>
        \n\nNote that the small image is not stretched, but simply centered in the view. Note also
        that longer dimension of wide and tall images fits the view exactly, while the other
        dimension is padded with whitespace.
    </string>
    <string
        name="matrix_desc"><i>The <b>MATRIX</b> ScaleType scales the image using the image\'s
        matrix when drawing. The image\'s matrix can be set using setImageMatrix(Matrix). In this
        case, we create a scaled trapezoidal effect by applying a polygon-to-polygon mapping.</i>
        \n\nNote that for this app, a simple mapping polygon is applied that scales the image à
        la FitXY, but which also decreases the length the top side, giving a trapezoidal effect.
    </string>

    <string
        name="image_cd">Image that demonstrates results of different scaleType options.</string>
</resources>
